# **Danny Pham**

## Software Engineer | Project Management | Financial Technology

New York, NY | dnnypham@gmail.com | (617)-602-5716 LinkedIn.com/in/dnnyp | GitHub: dnnyp | Portfolio: dnnyp.github.io

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a Software Engineer and Technical Project Manager who holds over four years of experience leading cross-functional initiatives in the financial technology space. As both a Project Manager and Software Engineer, I have an innate ability to balance the needs of the user against the business objectives of the company when designing interactive websites and applications.

### **SKILLS**

HTML5, CSS3/SASS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, React, Node.js, Express, Java, Ruby on Rails, SQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Redis, Jest, Enzyme, Cucumber, Puppeteer, Heroku, AWS, Atom, GitHub, Jira, IBM RTC, ServiceNow, Adobe Photoshop

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Web Development Intern**

Boston, MA

**Inclusion Org** 

January 2020 – Present

- Designed and implemented unit tests for React and Node applications using Jest
- · Created continuous integration workflows with GitHub Actions

## **Software Engineering Fellow**

Boston, MA

General Assembly

July 2019 – October 2019

- Participated in 500+ hours of applied training in software engineering and web development concepts focusing on front-end and back-end development
- Built skills and fluency in JavaScript, React, Node, Express, and other web development frameworks
- Worked with UX Designers and Software Engineers to create full stack web applications for clients

#### **IT Project Analyst**

Boston, MA

State Street Corporation

June 2016 – July 2019

- Owned and prioritized the product backlog of an enterprise trading application as the voice of the customer
- Planned and coordinated ~4 production software releases and a disaster recovery test per year
- Spearheaded the implementation of a new business intelligence tool to replace 60+ Excel reports
- Facilitated the requirements phase for 8 new application modules by collaborating with global stakeholders

#### **EDUCATION**

## **University of Massachusetts Amherst**

Amherst, MA

BA in Economics

May 2016

Relevant Courses: Programming with Data Structures, Programming Methodology, Computer Systems Principles